elecdir.com 2018-07-07

# ElecDir - Electronics and Electrical Web Directory - Privacy Policy

elecdir.com is committed to protecting the privacy of the users of its website and services. We respect the privacy of all visitors to our website. 

**Personal Information  
** We want you to use and enjoy the website without having to reveal personal information. We do not collect any personal data from our visitors when they use our services. You can access, browse our web site without disclosing your personal data. 

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes only the user's domain name, but not the e-mail address.We collect our users’ IP addresses and information regarding the use of our website and services to help diagnose problems with our servers, track movement within our website and, if necessary, deny service to abusing visitors. We may also collect information related to the referring URL, access times and browser type. Unless required by law, we will not share our users’ personal information, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and usage information, except with their consent or in aggregate or anonymous form, with third parties.

**Cookies**  
We do not use cookies in our site but our advertisers may use cookies when serving ads in our site. We use outside ad companies like Google Adsense, Kontera to display ads on this site. These third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of their ads being served on this website. We do not have access to these information. Currently we work with the ad company: Google Adsense. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies. 

**Linked Sites**  
This site contains links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.  
Third party sites linked to and from the Site are not necessarily under our control. We shall have no responsibilities or liabilities whatsoever for the content or privacy practices of any such linked site or any link or linking program at any time. We do not necessarily endorse companies (or related products or services) to or from which the site is linked. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to the site, you do so entirely at your own risk. 

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**  
We reserves the right to modify its Privacy Policy at any time. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on our website so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us.
